<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Ticket Search</string>
    <string name="title_activity_stadiums_map">Ticket Search</string>
    <string name="show_teams">Show Teams</string>
    <string name="select_a_team">Select a team</string>
    <string name="stubhub_query">stubhubDocumentType:event AND description:%1$s AND -description:PARKING AND -description:Season Tickets AND -description:VIP AND -description:Tailgate AND ancestorGenreDescriptions:NFL</string>
    <string name="fetching_ticket_info_please_wait">Fetching ticket info, please wait…</string>
    <string name="error_fetching_ticket_info">An error occurred while fetching the ticket information.</string>
    <string name="tickets_available">Number of tickets still available: %1$d</string>
    <string name="event_description">Description: %1$s</string>
    <string name="event_date">Date: %1$s</string>
    <string name="event_venue">Venue: %1$s</string>
    <string name="no_events_found">Could not find any future home games for this team.</string>
    <string name="click_here_to_buy">(Click anywhere in this window to buy tickets)</string>
    <string name="first_launch_instructions">Welcome to Ticket Search.\n\nYou can use this app to check if there are any available tickets for your team\'s next home game, and if so, optionally go to StubHub to purchase tickets for that game.\n\nTo use, either:\n1) Find your team\'s stadium on the map and click the symbol. An info window will show.\n2) Use the team list to find and select your team. Once you select a team, the map will zoom to the team\'s stadium location and show the info window.\n\t* On a phone, click the \'Show Teams menu item\'.\n\t* On a tablet, the team list is already visible in the side panel.\n\nOnce the info window is shown, a request will be sent to StubHub to find games for the team. The next home game\'s information will be displayed in the info window, including the number of available tickets for that game. If there are no upcoming home games or the connection to StubHub fails, you won\'t be able to see the ticket info.\n\nYou can click anywhere in the info window to open your device\'s web browser to the event page for the game on stubhub.com. For the best experience, install the native StubHub app and click the \'View in app\' option. If you choose to use the \'View in browser\' option, there may be some issues with certain mobile browsers and StubHub\'s mobile web pages.\n\nEnjoy!</string>

</resources>
